compassfx.com 2014-05-20

# CompassFX | Forex | Forex Trading | Forex Minis | Online Currency Trading

## CompassFX - Member, National Futures Association (NFA # 0232832) 

### Disclaimer

Clients should read the account opening documentation, disclosure documents and trading regulations carefully so that they fully understand limitations to the policies regarding executions of stops and no deficit accounts.

#### Risk Warning

Trading foreign currencies in the spot Forex market is a highly risky form of investing. It is a demanding yet potentially profitable opportunity for experienced traders. Before trading in the Forex market, you should carefully consider investment objectives, level of experience and risk tolerance. It is important to only invest money you can afford to lose.

There is a high degree of risk in trading foreign currencies. Any market transaction involving currencies contains risks including, but not limited to, the potential for random political events and economic conditions that may significantly affect the market price or liquidity of a currency.

Furthermore, the use of high leverage in trading margin accounts means that any market movement will have an equally proportional effect on deposited funds. This may work in your favor or not. There is the possibility that you could sustain a total loss of funds deposited when you trade spot currencies should the market move against your positions. Traders may lower their exposure to risk by employing risk-reducing strategies such as stop-loss or limit orders. 

There are also risks associated with utilizing an internet-based deal execution software application including, but not limited, to the failure of hardware and software. 

#### Privacy Policy

Compass FX truly values each and every one of our visitors and we take your privacy seriously. As part of our normal operations we may collect information about you and how you interact with our website. Our Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with a full description of the information we collect about you and what we do with that information. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at Support.

**Personally Identifiable Information** – In general, you can visit the Compass FX website without telling us who you are and without revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we might request that you disclose certain pieces of personal information to us. You may choose to disclose this information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address. Please note that if you choose not to disclose this information, functionality of our site may be limited. This personally identifiable information is never rented, sold or disclosed to any third parties.

**Cookies** – Compass FX collects anonymous user information through the delivery of cookies. The use of cookies is an industry standard and is currently used on most major Web sites. Cookies allow the Compass FX website to be more efficient by allowing us to learn what information is important to our visitors, and what isn't. A cookie will not allow a website to learn any personally identifiable information unless you have previously disclosed that information to us. A cookie allows websites to serve its customers better by providing measurement statistics on site usage. While Compass FX does not require you to accept cookies, certain services will not function properly if you do not use and accept cookies. We consider privacy and security of our visitors to be of the utmost importance. Any future development of Compass FX that involves the exchange of personally identifiable information will be treated with due discretion and will be fully disclosed to our visitors.

Back to Top

## Navigate CompassFX

## Trade Desk Support

## Quick Help
